# KAESIDE IWUAGWU

# Front End Web Developer

C: 201-956-7787 | Kaeside.iwuagwu@gmail.com | github.com/kaeside | http://www.kaeside.com

#### **PROFILE**

Front End Web Developer and experienced engineer with expertise in civil engineering and information technology. Martial artist and avid reader. Loves to learn new design through refactoring, test-driven development, and advocate of the user first experience.

#### PROGRAMMING SKILLS

JavaScript, React.js, jQuery, Node,js, HTML5 & CSS3, SASS, LESS, MongoDB, Mongoose, Git, Heroku

### **PROJECTS**

<u>EatUp</u>: Full Stack React JS app that joins people that want to eat the same type of food at a top rated restaurant in their city.

CozyFi: Full Stack React JS app that lists user generated coworking spaces along with their features within your area.

GigIt: React JS and Socket IO chat app that allows users from across the globe to chat with one another.

ISS Tracker: React Native iOS app that tracks the location of the International Space Station.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Manny Designs - Toronto, Canada - Remote Position

September 2016 - Present

Software Engineer Intern

Intern that develops and assists lead engineer in development of web and mobile apps using React JS and React Native.

### Thinkful - New York City, NY

**April 2016 - August 2016** 

Student

Intensive, four month program in modern full stack JavaScript web development. Covered topics including responsive mobile-first web development, UI development with React and vanilla JavaScript, testing with Mocha and Chai and full stack JavaScript development with Node.js. Collaborated daily with fellow students and with a senior web developer through pair programming and Git / GitHub.

# Maser Consulting - Mount Arlington, NJ

November 2013 - April 2016

Senior Engineer

Designed distributed antenna systems, from a civil engineering perspective, of cellular sites and network expansion for major telecommunications providers such as Verizon Wireless, AT&T, T-Mobile, and Sprint in the Greater NYC area, New England, and Central Maryland.

#### Englewood Hospital and Medical Center - Englewood, NJ

#### Outreach Desktop Support Analyst

**July 2012 - November 2013** 

Lead Analyst, Project Lead, and Technical Support Representative for the Medical Associates of Englewood Hospital and Medical Center (EHMC), responsible for overseeing the integration of private practices into EHMC's infrastructure, supporting the legacy systems of private practices, and support for any infrastructure related issues pertaining to the private practices.

Service Desk Analyst

**July 2007 - July 2012** 

Lead in-house analyst for after-hours and weekend support. Provided levels one and two technical support for EHMC's main campus and level one and remote support for EHMC's satellite sites. Created support documentation for common and unique incidents and implemented mobile tech solution for full-time staff service desk analysts.

### Seven Seas Engineering - Parsippany, NJ

June 2008 - August 2008

Junior Inspector

Inspected and identified structural deficiencies of the George Washington Bridge's Port Authority facilities and parking decks of the JFK International Airport. Worked closely with the senior draftsman to develop final reports submitted to the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey that included CAD drawings, pictures of structural deficiencies, descriptions of structural deficiencies, recommended solutions to deficiencies and level of urgency.

#### **EDUCATION**

New Jersey Institute of Technology - Newark, NJ

Bachelor of Science - Civil Engineering

President of NJIT Chapter of Pi Kappa Phi and President of NJIT Chapter of the American Society of Civil Engineer	:s